(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,n,t){},14:function(e,n,t){},15:function(e,n,t){"use strict";t.r(n);var s=t(0),r=t.n(s),a=t(6),o=t.n(a),i=t(1),h=t(2),u=t(3),c=t(4),l=(t(13),[{question:"Where do most of the events in Game of Thrones take place?",answers:["Northeros","Easteros","Westeros"],rightAnswer:"Westeros",id:"128471"},{question:" Who shot the burning arrow that sunk Lord Hoster Tully\u2019s ship at his funeral?",answers:["Brynden Tully","Edmure Tully","WestCatelyn Tullyeros"],rightAnswer:"Brynden Tully",id:"128472"},{question:"For how many kings did Lord Tywin Lannister serve as Hand?",answers:["0","2","3"],rightAnswer:"3",id:"123457"},{question:"\u201cA crow gone bad. A man gone mad. A people so had. A North so sad.\u201d Who said these lines?",answers:["Jon Snow","Mance Rayder","Bran Stark"],rightAnswer:"Mance Rayder",id:"123447"},{question:"Which of these was The King Who Knelt?",answers:["Eddard Stark","Mikken Stark","Torrhen Stark"],rightAnswer:"Torrhen Stark",id:"122457"},{question:"Patchface came from which of the Free Cities?",answers:["Valyria","Lorath","Volantis"],rightAnswer:"Volantis",id:"113457"},{question:"Where did Lyanna die?",answers:["The Tower of Joy","Winterfell","The Shadow Tower"],rightAnswer:"The Tower of Joy",id:"133457"},{question:"Who forged Arya\u2019s sword, Needle?",answers:["Donal Noye","Mikken","Tobho Mott"],rightAnswer:"Mikken",id:"143457"},{question:"Which language is commonly spoken in the Game of Thrones?",answers:["Valyrian","Old English","Norse"],rightAnswer:"Valyrian",id:"153457"},{question:"How many robbers died in the heist?",answers:["One","Three","Four"],rightAnswer:"Three",id:"163457"},{question:"What is The professor's real name?",answers:["Agustin Ramos","Sergio Marquina","Andr\xe9s de Fonollosa"],rightAnswer:"Sergio Marquina",id:"173547"},{question:"Raquel's mother has how many daughters?",answers:["2","1","4"],rightAnswer:"2",id:"183547"},{question:"Inspector Raquel's mother suffered from which medical condition?",answers:["Parkinson's disease","Alzheimer's disease","Congestive heart failure"],rightAnswer:"Alzheimer's disease",id:"193457"},{question:"How many people did the professor recruit to help him carry out his plan?",answers:["Nine","Seven","Eight"],rightAnswer:"Eight",id:"202475"},{question:"Whose idea and plan was for the heist?",answers:["The professor's father","The professor's","Angel"],rightAnswer:"The professor's father",id:"210245"}]),d=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:5;return Promise.resolve(l.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()})).slice(0,e))},w=t(7),m=(t(14),function(e){Object(c.a)(t,e);var n=Object(u.a)(t);function t(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,r=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)r[a]=arguments[a];return(e=n.call.apply(n,[this].concat(r))).state={userAnswer:Object(w.a)(e.props.answers)},e.setAnswer=function(n){e.setState({userAnswer:[n]})},e}return Object(h.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},r.a.createElement("div",null,this.props.question),r.a.createElement("div",{className:"answerButtons"},this.state.userAnswer.map((function(n){return r.a.createElement("input",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-info answerButton",onClick:function(){e.setAnswer(n),e.props.selected(n)},value:n})}))))}}]),t}(s.Component)),f=function(e){Object(c.a)(t,e);var n=Object(u.a)(t);function t(){var e;Object(i.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,r=new Array(s),a=0;a<s;a++)r[a]=arguments[a];return(e=n.call.apply(n,[this].concat(r))).state={questions:[],score:0,responses:0},e.getQuestions=function(){d().then((function(n){e.setState({questions:n})}))},e.computerScore=function(n,t){n===t&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({responses:e.state.responses+1})},e}return Object(h.a)(t,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.getQuestions()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quizBox"},r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quizHeader"},r.a.createElement("h3",null,"QUIZ")),this.state.responses<5?this.state.questions.map((function(n){return r.a.createElement(m,{question:n.question,answers:n.answers,correctAnswer:n.rightAnswer,selected:function(t){return e.computerScore(t,n.rightAnswer)},rightAnswerflag:e.state.rightAnswerflag})})):r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("h1",null,"Your score is : ",this.state.score,"/5"),r.a.createElement("input",{type:"button",className:"btn btn-success tryAgain",value:"Try again",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload(!1)}})))}}]),t}(s.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));o.a.render(r.a.createElement(r.a.StrictMode,null,r.a.createElement(f,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))},8:function(e,n,t){e.exports=t(15)}},[[8,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.0b0df27a.chunk.js.map